Now that you've seen how the PCA library works in scikit-learn,
现在你已经看到了如何使用 scikit-learn 中的 PCA 库
and you fit it to the handwritten digits dataset,
并将其拟合手写数字数据集
we should take a closer look at exactly what
那么我们应该更仔细地了解
PCA gives us back and what these different parts mean.
PCA 究竟给我们返回什么 以及这些不同部分的含义
Let's pick up where we left off in the last video.
让我们接着上一个视频的结尾开始
Here, I've read in the necessary libraries and
在这里 我导入了要用到的库
split the image data into a label and the features,
并将图像数据分割为标签和特征
which are the pixels in the actual image.
这些特征是实际图像中的像素
Let's take a look at the top 30.
让我们看看前 30个图像
Now, using the do_PCA function you saw earlier,
现在 使用前面看到的 do_pca 函数
let's create the PCA model,
让我们创建 PCA 模型
as well as the X_PCA component.
以及 x_pca 矩阵
If we look at the PCA model,
如果我们看这个 PCA 模型
we can hit dot tab to see a whole bunch of things that are available on this.
我们可以先点击 dot 键再点击 tab 键 来查看这上面有很多可用的东西
Some of the things that I usually pay attention to are,
我通常注意的一些是
so there's explained_variance_ratio, is usually really helpful,
这里有 explained_variance_ratio  通常是非常有用
and the number of components,
还有成分的数量
the number of features.
特征的数量
If you look at your PCA model and put a dot tab,
如果你查看你的 PCA 模型 点击 dot 键再点击 tab 键
you can see a bunch of things that are available.
你可以看到一堆可用的东西
Let's take a look at what some of these things do for our model.
让我们看看这些东西对我们的模型有什么作用
So, in the notebook below,
在下面的 notebook 中
you'll see there's the scree_plot function.
你会看到有一个 scree_plot 函数
This function plots the amount of variance explained by each component.
此函数用于绘制由每个成分所解释的变化量
Let's see what this looks like.
让我们看看它是什么样子
Notice that we have 15 bars,
注意 我们有15个柱
each associated with one of our principle components.
每个柱都与我们的一个主成分相关
If you remember, up here,
如果你还记得 在这里
we fit 15 principal components.
我们拟合了 15个主成分
Then, the height of the bar is the amount of variability from
然后 柱的高度是由
the original feature set that's explained by that component.
该成分所解释的原始特征集的变化量
So, for our first component,
所以 对于我们的第一个成分
six percent of the available variability
全部数据的总变化量中
and all of the data is explained by that component.
有 6% 的可由该成分解释
Then, for the second component,
然后 对于第二个成分
4.29 percent of the total variability is explained by that component,
总变化量的 4.29% 可由该成分解释
and so on and so forth.
其余以此类推
The total amount of variability explained by all
所有 15 个主成分所解释的变化量
15 of the first component is about 35 percent,
约为占总变化量的 35%
which you can see by this line.
你可以通过这条线看到
These principal components can help you understand how many you want to
如我所解释的 这些主成分可以帮助你了解
keep because of how much variance in the original data as I explained.
如何根据原始数据的方差来决定保留多少主成分
This is one way to create a metric for an unsupervised algorithm.
这是为非监督算法创建度量的一种方法
This is one way to understand how well
这是一种了解
unsupervised algorithm is doing at predicting what's happening with your data.
非监督算法在预测数据时性能好坏的方法
The other thing that we should look at is how
另一件我们应该看看的事情是
these components relate back to the original images.
这些主成分是如何与原始图像联系起来的
The next function that you see in the notebook is called plot_component.
你在这个 notebook 中看到的下一个函数是 plot_component
What this does is it highlights the pixels
它的作用是突出显示
in the image that are important for each component.
图像中对每个成分都很重要的像素
So, if we look at the first component,
所以 如果我们使用这个函数
the zero's component using this function,
来查看第一个成分 即 0 成分
you can see that it's probably picking out zeros from your dataset.
你可以看到它正在从你的数据集中提取 0 的图像
If we look at other components,
如果我们看看其他成分
you can see that this is picking out some other patterns in the images
你会发现这是在图像中挑选一些其他模式
that are related to being able to differentiate them from one another.
这些模式与能够将它们彼此区别开来有关
Essentially, these bright yellow pixels or
本质上 这些亮黄色像素或大权重像素
heavy weights and these darker blue pixels are lighter weights
和这些深蓝色像素或较轻权重像素
associated with how much that pixel matters
与它们对该特定成分的
for this particular component. Now, it's your turn.
重要性相关联 现在轮到你了